Guide to the Cecily Brownstone Papers MSS.134
Fales Library and Special Collections
Cecily Brownstone Papers
1940-2005
Fales Library and Special Collections
Brownstone, Cecily
MSS.134
38 Linear Feet 31 records cartons, 18 document cases
Cecily Brownstone was the Associated Press food editor for nearly forty years, as well as the author of Cecily Brownstone's Associated Press Cookbook (Associated Press, 1972). Brownstone amassed a comprehensive collection of materials relating to American cookery, including cookbooks, pamphlets, postcards, menus, recipe boxes, and more.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Cecily Brownstone Papers were purchased by Fales Library in 2002 from Cecily Brownstone.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Biographical Note
Cecily Brownstone was born in Plum Coulee, Manitoba, Canada, in 1909, and grew up in Winnipeg, the fourth of five sisters. She attended the University of Manitoba and came to New York City to pursue her studies and to work. She lived in Greenwich Village, appropriately enough in a brownstone house, in a duplex apartment that included a spectacular test kitchen, and that housed her large cookbook collection.
Cecily Brownstone was The Associated Press Food Editor from 1947 to 1986 -- for thirty-nine years. During that time she was the most widely published of syndicated food writers. The five recipe columns and two food features she wrote for the A.P. each week appeared in papers all over the United States, in addition to a number of other countries.
Earlier in her career as a journalist, Brownstone was the Food Editor of Parent's Magazine, and the Child Care Editor of Family Circle magazine. She also wrote a book for children, All Kinds of Mothers, illustrated by her niece, the artist Miriam Brofsky Kley.
Brownstone was also a consultant to Carl Sontheimer, president of Cuisinart, a physicist, entrepreneur, and founder of the food processor industry in America. With Sontheimer, Brownstone edited the highly regarded magazine, Pleasures of Cooking, and wrote Classic Cakes and Other Great Cuisinart Desserts (Hearst Books, 1994). She earlier wrote Cecily Brownstone's Associated Press Cookbook (A.P., 1972).
Cecily Brownstone was a close friend and confident of James Beard and The Joy of Cooking authors, Irma Rombauer and Marion Rombauer Becker, and other noted cookbook and food writers. She and Beard telephoned each other almost daily, at 8 a.m., and their friendship is mentioned in two recent biographies of Beard. Brownstone's collection includes 93 letters and postcards from Irma Rombauer, and about 45 of Marion Becker's letters. During the last five years of Becker's life she phoned Brownstone for an hour every weekend; they were close friends, and Brownstone is mentioned often in Anne Mendelson's recent biography of Irma Rombauer and her daughter. Brownstone's collection includes signed, inscribed copies of almost every edition of The Joy of Cooking, sent to her first by Irma Rombauer, and later by Marion Becker.
The Joy of Cooking author Irma Rombauer called Cecily Brownstone "wonder child (and wonder woman)."
New York Times food columnist Molly O'Neil called Brownstone one of the "cornerstones of authentic cooking in New York."
On Brownstone's retirement, former New York Times Food Editor Jane Nickerson wrote: "Of syndicated food writers, she's been the most widely read." Nickerson added: Brownstone's recipes were always "unusual, appetizing, and accurate down to the last one-eighth of a teaspoon of salt." Brownstone's "success derived, in my view, from her sensitivity to readers' tastes and her insistence that recipes give high, appealing results."
Cecily Brownstone died on August 30, 2005 at the age of 96.
Scope and Content Note
The Cecily Brownstone Papers is a diverse collection of materials, including correspondence, press releases, photographs, publicity, articles and recipes authored by Brownstone, general food-related articles and recipes authored by others, calendars, notes, manuscript recipe books, photocopied cookbooks, bibliographical inventories, a menu collection, a postcard collection, a recipe box collection, a pamphlet collection, and videotapes relating to the food industry.
Series Description
Series I: Author Files
Series II: Articles and Recipes
Series III: Personal Files
Series IV: Brownstone's Notes
Series V: Manuscript Recipe Books
Series VI: Photocopied Cookbooks
Series VII: Bibliographical Inventories
Subseries A: Index Card File
Series VIII: Menu Collection
Series IX: Postcard Collection
Series X: Ephemera
Series XI: Video recordings
Series XII: Recipe Box Collection
Series XIII: Pamphlet Collection
Subseries A: Miscellaneous Printed Material
Oversize
Arrangement
The Cecily Brownstone Papers are organized into fourteen series. Within these series, files are arranged both alphabetically by subject/author heading and chronologically depending on the nature of the series. Descriptions are at the folder level.
Related Material at Fales Library and Special Collections
Marion Nestle Food Studies Collection (https://guides.nyu.edu/speccol/food-studies)
Les Dames d'Escoffier New York Archive (MSS.150)
James Beard Papers (MSS.263)
Separated Material
The Cecily Brownstone Papers were largely culled from within Brownstone's larger library of American cookery. Brownstone's book library has been catalogued separately from the personal papers. A related name search in Bobcat under "Cecily Brownstone" will retrieve records for the entire library, consisting of over 8400 titles.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact the Fales Library with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Clippings (information artifacts); Card files.; Notes.; Pamphlets.; Cooking, American -- History -- 20th century.; Food industry and trade; Books.; Calendars.; Videocassettes.; New York (N.Y.).; Buttons (information artifacts).; Postcards.; Joy of cooking.; Correspondence.; Culinary industry.; Dinners and dining -- New York.; Dinners and dining -- United States -- History.; Family circle.; Fliers (printed matter); Gastronomy.; Parents' magazine.; Menus.; Photographs.; Recipes.; Sontheimer, Carl G.; Beard, James, 1903-1985; The Associated Press; Becker, Marion Rombauer; Les Dames d'Escoffier International; Cuisinart (Firm); Parents' Magazine Enterprises; Child, Julia; Rombauer, Irma von Starkloff, 1877-1962
- Series I: Author Files
  Arrangement
  Author files arranged alphabetically.
  - Acton, Eliza, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adams, Charlotte, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Adams, Harriet, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Adolph, Phila, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Aileen, Paul, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Albright, Nancy, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alda, Robert and Flora, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Allen, Ida Baily, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Allen, Jana and Margaret Gin, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Allison, Sonia, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Anderson, Jess, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Angier, Bradford, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Aresty, Ester, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Arkin, Frieda, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Armitage, Merle, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Arsdale, May, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Arum, Nancy, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Asquith, Pamella, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Atiyeh, Wadeeha, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Atkins, Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Atlanta Music Club, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Atlas, Nava, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Attali, Michel, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Aurell, Walter, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Axler, Bruce, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Ayto, John, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Bacon, Josephine, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Bailey, Lee, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bailey, Pearl, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Baner, Helen and Roberta Logerman, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Barber, Edith, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Barbour, Beverly, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Barkas, Janet, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Barron's, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bateman, Ruth, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Batist, Bessie, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Baum, Ruth and Hilary, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bear, John and Marina, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Beard, James, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Beard, James (photographs), undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - James Beard Foundation, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Beatrice Foods Co., undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Becker, Gail, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Becker, Marion [Becker family], undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Beecher, Catherine, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Beecher, Henry Ward, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Beer, Gretel, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Beeton, Isabella, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Beinert, Frederica, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Bell, Judith, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Bell, Mille, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Bellin, Mildred, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Benet, Jane, undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Bennett, Iva and Martha Simon, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Bennett, Victor, undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Benoit, Jehane, undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Beranbaum, Rose, undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Berg, Gertrude, undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Bergerson, Victor [Trader Vic], undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Berglund, Berndt and Clare Bolsby, undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Berkoff, Nancy, undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Bernachon, Jean-Jacques, undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Bernal, Arthur, undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Better Homes and Gardens, undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Bingham, Joan, undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Bishop, Jack, undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Blackwood, Frances, undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Blakely, Linda, undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Blanch, Lesley, undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Blank, Ruth, undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Blohm, Hannelore and H.D. Cremer, undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Blount, Allison, undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Bon Appátit, undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Bond, Carolyn, undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Booker, Emma, undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Boorman, Sylvia, undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Booth, George, undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Bothwell, Jean, undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Bouterin, Antoine, undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Bowser, Pearl and Joan Eckstein, undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Bracken, Peg, undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Bradshaw, George, undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Braider, Carol, undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Brassel, Helen, undated (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Brauá, John, undated (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Brennan, Dick and Ella, undated (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Brenner, Eleanor, undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Brenner, Leslie, undated (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Bride's Magazine, undated (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Briggs, Richard, undated (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Brown, Ed, undated (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Brown, Gene et al., undated (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Brown, Helen Evans, undated (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Brown, Philip, undated (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Brown, Stephen, undated (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Brunner, Edward, undated (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Bruyere, Toni and Sidney Robey, undated (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Bryan, Lettice, undated (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Buckley, Peter, undated (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Bullock, Helen, undated (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Bullwinkel, Madeleine, undated (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Bunnelle, Hasse, undated (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Burgess, Claudia, undated (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Burrows, Fredrika, undated (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Burrows, Lois and Laura Myers, undated (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Burt, Elinor, undated (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Burum, Linda, undated (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Burwash, Peter, undated (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Butler, Cleora, undated (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Cagle, William, undated (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Calingaert, Efrem and Jacquelyn Serwer, undated (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Callen, Anna, undated (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Callvert, Isabel, undated (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Campbell Soup Co., undated (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Campbell, Thora, undated (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Candler, Teresa, undated (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Cannon, Poppy, undated (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Cannon, Trudy, undated (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Cantwell, Mary, undated (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Capsouto, Jacques, undated (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Carlisle, Helen, undated (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Carmack, Robert and Gino Cofacci, undated (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Carper, Jean, undated (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Carrier, Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Carson, Gerald, undated (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Carter, Susannah, undated (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Caruba, Rebecca, undated (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Cary, Elisabeth and Annie Jones, undated (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Cavin, Ruth, undated (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Celli, Elisa, undated (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Chalmers, Irena, undated (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Chamberlain, Samuel, undated (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Chambers, Mary, undated (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Chappellet, Molly, undated (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Charpentier, Henri, undated (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Chase, Alvin, undated (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Chase, Emily, undated (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Chase, Ilka, undated (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Chen, Helen, undated (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Chen, Yung-chi Chao, undated (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Chesman, Andrea, undated (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Child, Julia and Paul, undated (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Child, Lydia Maria, undated (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Chilton Book Company, undated (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Chioffi, Nancy and Gretchen Mead, undated (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Choate, Judith, undated (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Chocolatier, undated (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Chu, Grace, undated (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - Church, Ruth Ellen, undated (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - Churchill, Arabella, undated (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - Claiborne, Craig, undated (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - Clarke, Oz, undated (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - Clayton, Bernard, undated (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - Clements Library, University of Michigan, undated (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - Clifford, William, undated (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Clifton, Claire, undated (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - Coco Palms, undated (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - Cole, Sally, undated (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Coleman, Arthur, undated (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - Collier, Carole, undated (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Colwin, Laurie, undated (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - Conason, Emil and Ella Person, undated (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Conway, Madeleine and Nancy Kirk, undated (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - Conwell, Barbara, undated (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Cook, Joan, undated (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Cook, Margaret, undated (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - Coon, Nelson, undated (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - Cooperative Extension Service, Washington State University, undated (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - Corbitt, Helen, undated (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - Corlin, Judith, undated (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Corson, Juliet, undated (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - Cosman, Madeleine, undated (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - Craig, Elizabeth, undated (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - Crary, Anne M., undated (Box 1, Folder 173 A)
  - Crawford, Frances, undated (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - Crawford, Patricia, undated (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - Creel, Henry, undated (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - Crenshaw, Mary Ann, undated (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - Crocker, Betty, undated (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - Croly, Jane, undated (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - Crosse, Victor, undated (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - Cuisinarts [Southeimer, Carl], undated (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - Cutler, Carol, undated (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - Czarnecki, Joseph, undated (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - D'Ermo, Dominique, undated (Box 1, Folder 184)
  - Dallas, E.S., undated (Box 1, Folder 185)
  - Dalsass, Diana, undated (Box 1, Folder 186)
  - Damerell, Edna, undated (Box 1, Folder 187)
  - Darack, Arthur et al, undated (Box 1, Folder 188)
  - David, Elizabeth, undated (Box 1, Folder 189)
  - Davids, Kenneth, undated (Box 1, Folder 190)
  - Davidson, Alan and Jane, undated (Box 1, Folder 191)
  - Davidson, Diane, undated (Box 1, Folder 192)
  - Davis, Helen Ayers, undated (Box 1, Folder 193)
  - Dawson, Tony, undated (Box 1, Folder 194)
  - De Groot, Katherine, undated (Box 1, Folder 195)
  - De Groot, Roy, undated (Box 1, Folder 196)
  - De Gros, J.H., undated (Box 1, Folder 197)
  - De Guoy, Louis, undated (Box 1, Folder 198)
  - De Knight, Freda, undated (Box 1, Folder 199)
  - De Plantina, Bartholomaius, undated (Box 1, Folder 200)
  - De Wolfe, Elsie, undated (Box 1, Folder 201)
  - Deacon, Richard, undated (Box 1, Folder 202)
  - Deane, Martha, undated (Box 1, Folder 203)
  - DeBolt, Margaret, undated (Box 1, Folder 204)
  - Cy DeCosse Incorporated, undated (Box 1, Folder 205)
  - Deighton, Len, undated (Box 1, Folder 206)
  - Delmonico, John and Peter, undated (Box 1, Folder 207)
  - Deutsch, Ronald, undated (Box 2, Folder 208)
  - Dick, Erma, undated (Box 2, Folder 209)
  - DiLauro, Nelda, undated (Box 2, Folder 210)
  - Dillin, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 211)
  - Dollaghan, Helen, undated (Box 2, Folder 212)
  - Dorn, Frank, undated (Box 2, Folder 213)
  - Downes, Muriel, undated (Box 2, Folder 214)
  - Doxat, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 215)
  - Dragonwagon, Cresent, undated (Box 2, Folder 216)
  - Drew, Edwin, undated (Box 2, Folder 217)
  - Dreyfus, Michel, undated (Box 2, Folder 218)
  - Dribin, Lois and Susan Ivankovich, undated (Box 2, Folder 219)
  - Duijker, Hubrecht, undated (Box 2, Folder 220)
  - Dull, Henrietta, undated (Box 2, Folder 221)
  - Dumas, Alexandre, undated (Box 2, Folder 222)
  - [Duncan], Rea, undated (Box 2, Folder 223)
  - Duperret, Jean-Yves, undated (Box 2, Folder 224)
  - Dupree, Nathalie, undated (Box 2, Folder 225)
  - Duquette, Susan, undated (Box 2, Folder 226)
  - Durkee, Jean, undated (Box 2, Folder 227)
  - Duson, Will, undated (Box 2, Folder 228)
  - Dyer, Ceil, undated (Box 2, Folder 229)
  - Eastman, Margaret, undated (Box 2, Folder 230)
  - Echols, Barbara, undated (Box 2, Folder 231)
  - Egerton, March, undated (Box 2, Folder 232)
  - Elisofon, Eliot, undated (Box 2, Folder 233)
  - Elkon, Juliette, undated (Box 2, Folder 234)
  - Elliot, Sharon, undated (Box 2, Folder 235)
  - Emerling, Carol and Eugene Jonckers, undated (Box 2, Folder 236)
  - Emery, Carla, undated (Box 2, Folder 237)
  - Ensrud, Barbara, undated (Box 2, Folder 238)
  - Ephron, Nora, undated (Box 2, Folder 239)
  - Eschelman, Ruthe and Mary Winston, undated (Box 2, Folder 240)
  - Escoffier, Auguste, undated (Box 2, Folder 241)
  - Estragon, Vladimir, undated (Box 2, Folder 242)
  - Evans, Michele, undated (Box 2, Folder 243)
  - Fadiman, Clifton, undated (Box 2, Folder 244)
  - Farmer, Fannie, undated (Box 2, Folder 245)
  - Farmington, undated (Box 2, Folder 246)
  - Feezor, Betty, undated (Box 2, Folder 247)
  - Feig, Barbara, undated (Box 2, Folder 248)
  - Ferber, Edna, undated (Box 2, Folder 249)
  - Fern, Fanny, undated (Box 2, Folder 250)
  - Fernald, Merritt and Alfred Kinsey, undated (Box 2, Folder 251)
  - Fielding, Daphne, undated (Box 2, Folder 252)
  - Fields, Alonzo, undated (Box 2, Folder 253)
  - Fillin, Lucille, undated (Box 2, Folder 254)
  - Finsand, Mary, undated (Box 2, Folder 255)
  - Firnstahl, Timothy, undated (Box 2, Folder 256)
  - Fisher, Abby, undated (Box 2, Folder 257)
  - Fisher, M.K.F., undated (Box 2, Folder 258)
  - Fitzgerald, Mollie, undated (Box 2, Folder 259)
  - Fleming, Diana, undated (Box 2, Folder 260)
  - Fletcher, Mattie Bell, undated (Box 2, Folder 261)
  - Flores, Ana Gloria, undated (Box 2, Folder 262)
  - Fougner, G. Selmer, undated (Box 2, Folder 263)
  - Fowler, Halstead, undated (Box 2, Folder 264)
  - Fox, Helen, undated (Box 2, Folder 265)
  - Frampton, Mary, undated (Box 2, Folder 266)
  - Francatelli, Charles, undated (Box 2, Folder 267)
  - Francescani, Maureen, undated (Box 2, Folder 268)
  - Franey, Pierre, undated (Box 2, Folder 269)
  - Frank, Dorothy, undated (Box 2, Folder 270)
  - Frazier, Claude, undated (Box 2, Folder 271)
  - Frederick, J. George, undated (Box 2, Folder 272)
  - Frucht, Phyllis et al, undated (Box 2, Folder 273)
  - Furman, Bess, undated (Box 2, Folder 274)
  - Fussell, Betty, undated (Box 2, Folder 275)
  - Gaskins, Ruth, undated (Box 2, Folder 276)
  - Gault, Henri, undated (Box 2, Folder 277)
  - Gelink, Barbara, undated (Box 2, Folder 278)
  - George, Jean, undated (Box 2, Folder 279)
  - George, Phyllis and Bill Adler, undated (Box 2, Folder 280)
  - Gerras, Charles, undated (Box 2, Folder 281)
  - Gerson, Sylvia and Mildred Covert, undated (Box 2, Folder 282)
  - Gewanter, Vera and Dorothy Parker, undated (Box 2, Folder 283)
  - Gibbons, Barbara, undated (Box 2, Folder 284)
  - Gibbons, Euell, undated (Box 2, Folder 285)
  - Giehl, Dudley, undated (Box 2, Folder 286)
  - Gilchrist, Joelyn and Jacqueline Wood, undated (Box 2, Folder 287)
  - Gillette, F.L. and Hugo Ziemann, undated (Box 2, Folder 288)
  - Gilletz, Norene, undated (Box 2, Folder 289)
  - Gin, Margaret, undated (Box 2, Folder 290)
  - Glenn, Camille, undated (Box 2, Folder 291)
  - Gold Medal Flour, undated (Box 2, Folder 292)
  - Goldbeck, Nikki, undated (Box 2, Folder 293)
  - Goldberg, Larry, undated (Box 2, Folder 294)
  - Goldsmith, Mureen, undated (Box 2, Folder 295)
  - Gonzalez, Elaine, undated (Box 2, Folder 296)
  - Good Housekeeping, undated (Box 2, Folder 297)
  - Goodfellow, Barbara, undated (Box 2, Folder 298)
  - Goodfellow, Elizabeth, undated (Box 2, Folder 299)
  - Goodman, Linda, undated (Box 2, Folder 300)
  - Goodman, Raymond and Joseph Durocher, undated (Box 2, Folder 301)
  - Gordon, Elizabeth, undated (Box 2, Folder 302)
  - Gottfried, Jeremiah, undated (Box 2, Folder 303)
  - Gotto, Antonio and Helen Roe, undated (Box 2, Folder 304)
  - Goulart, Frances, undated (Box 2, Folder 305)
  - Gould, Bruce, undated (Box 2, Folder 306)
  - Gourmet, undated (Box 2, Folder 307)
  - Gouy, Louis, undated (Box 2, Folder 308)
  - Graham, Gladys, undated (Box 2, Folder 309)
  - Gray, Patience and Primrose Boyd, undated (Box 2, Folder 310)
  - Green, Karen, undated (Box 2, Folder 311)
  - Greene, Gloria, undated (Box 2, Folder 312)
  - Greif, Martin, undated (Box 2, Folder 313)
  - Griffith, Corinne, undated (Box 2, Folder 314)
  - Grocery Store Products Co., undated (Box 2, Folder 315)
  - Groene, Janet, undated (Box 2, Folder 316)
  - Gross, Mary Anne, undated (Box 2, Folder 317)
  - Grossman, Bob and Ruth, undated (Box 2, Folder 318)
  - Grosvenor, Verta, undated (Box 2, Folder 319)
  - Guárard, Michel, undated (Box 2, Folder 320)
  - Gundel, Charles, undated (Box 2, Folder 321)
  - Gwathmey, Emily, undated (Box 2, Folder 322)
  - Hackley, Sharon, undated (Box 2, Folder 323)
  - Haedrich, Ken, undated (Box 2, Folder 324)
  - Haiken, Lee, undated (Box 2, Folder 325)
  - Haines, Edith, undated (Box 2, Folder 326)
  - Hale, Sarah, undated (Box 2, Folder 327)
  - Hall, Alan, undated (Box 2, Folder 328)
  - Halpern, Daniel and Julie Strand, undated (Box 2, Folder 329)
  - Hamm, Marie, undated (Box 2, Folder 330)
  - Hanle, Zack, undated (Box 2, Folder 331)
  - Hannum, Hurst and Robert Blumberg, undated (Box 2, Folder 332)
  - Hansen, Barbara, undated (Box 2, Folder 333)
  - Hardman, Michael, undated (Box 2, Folder 334)
  - Harland, Marion, undated (Box 2, Folder 335)
  - Harlech, Pamela, undated (Box 2, Folder 336)
  - Harrington, Geri, undated (Box 2, Folder 337)
  - Harrington, Ty, undated (Box 2, Folder 338)